## EGBOH CHINYE CYNTHIA

No. 32 Barika street, U.I, Ibadan. Nigeria.

Tel: 08036315984, 08051983185.

Email: <a href="mailto:chinye31@gmail.com">chinye31@gmail.com</a>

### **CAREER OBJECTIVE:**

To provide top quality service in a challenging and merit driven work environment with opportunity for career development and advantage. To contribute effectively to the scientific research development, quality control, and strategic planning objectives of your organization.

### **SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES:**

- Strategic planning and ability to handle pressure sensibly and maintain poise in the face of demanding situation while keeping focus on the execution of the desired result.
- High numerical and analytical proficiency with keen attention to details.
- Time management and Ability to work independently with minimum supervision.
- Ability to teach others for better understanding
- Excellent, verbal and written communication skills
- Proficiency in the use of Microsoft Office suites.

### **PERSONAL DATA:**

Date of birth: 31/12/1985

Sex: Female

Marital Status: Single

Local Government Area: Aniocha-north

State of origin: Delta

Nationality: Nigerian

### EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTIONS ATTENDED WITH DATES:

Delta State University, Abraka. (2010-2013)

D.S.C Technical High School, Warri. (1997-2003)

D.S.C Model Primary School III (1991-1997)

### **QUALIFICATIONS OBTAINED WITH DATES:**

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc) in Biochemistry	2013
Senior School Certificate Examination (SSCE)	2003
First School Leaving Certificate Examination	1997

## **PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:**

Certificate in Health, Security, Safety and Environment I, II, III. (2015)

Certificate of Proficiency in Human Resources and Skill Acquisition (2011)

### **WORKING EXPERIENCE:**

# **Abiodun Metropolitan College, 2017-till date**Barika, Ibadan,Oyo State.

DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

Chemistry and Basic Science teacher Monitored each student's development as the class teacher Organize Social activities for Students

# Faith Shuttle Service, 2016-2017

### Warri, Delta State.

DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES
 Transport Coordinator/Marketer

Marketers, enlists students for

shuttle service and coordinates drivers.

# Government Day Secondary School, 2014-2015

### Charanchi, Katsina State.

 DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES NYSC

Chemistry Teacher
Making notes and conducting class assessment

## African Research Laboratories (ARL), 2012-2013

## Otorho-Agbon, Ethiope East Local Government Area, Delta State.

• DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

# **Laboratory Scientist**Preparation of buffer solutions

DNA extraction
Transaminase tests (AST and ALT), etc.

### **REFERENCES**

Available on Request